IGOR IVANENKO

home: Belarus, Minsk

phone/viber: +375(29) 5574550 e-mail: <u>ivanenko.igor.88@gmail.com</u>

skype: <u>Igor Iv</u> telegram: <u>@ki11roy</u> LinkedIn: <u>Igor Ivanenko</u>



OBJECTIVE:

I'm a certified Salesforce developer. Started work in this technologies at 2018 year and keep working.

I start my professional IT career like a Java Developer. At free time I'm learning new technologies.

Looking for new opportunities to work in modern companies in the new teams on interesting projects as a developer.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

Programming Language: Java, Apex

Technologies: Lightning / Visualfore / LWC / Servlet / JSP / ¡Query

Web: JS / HTML / CSS / XML / Tomcat

Frameworks: NodeJS / Angular / Spring / Hibernate

Test Tools: JUnit / TestNG / DbUnit DB Languages: SOQL / SOSL / SQL

Other: Maven / Git / OOP / Design Patterns / MySQL

English: B2 (intermediate)

EDUCATION:

JetBI «ITstart» under the leadership of Pavel

Salesforce courses (1 month / 2018) Veinik (01.2018-04.2018)

VRPConsulting BNTU "Institute for Advanced Training and Salesforce courses Retraining of Personnel", Minsk (2012-2014)

(3 month / 2018)

Physics Faculty

itstart.by Chair: physics and informatics

Individual training at school of programming BPSU n.a. M. Tank, Minsk (2007-2012)

PROJECT:

https://github.com/killroy13/RestaurantReservationProject-SpringHibernate

Description: This is an electronic system of reserving places in restaurants. The application allows you to find the best place for rest and entertainment, to learn information about the restaurant and to focus on reviews from other customers (users) when choosing.

Used technologies: JDBC, DAO, Servlets, MVC, JSP, Spring, JPA, Hibernate, Ajax, jQuery, Tomcat, Maven, MySQL

EXPERIENCE:

VRPConsulting High School

Salesforce Developer (2018-) System administrator/teacher (2011-2014)

Evrotorg freelance

Software Support Specialist (2014-2018) Work with vector graphics